Inventory of the Richard Throssel Papers, 1900-1993 (bulk 1902-1933)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Richard Throssel papers
1900-1993
1902-1933
Throssel, Richard, d. 1933
02394
23.45 cubic ft. (61 boxes)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Collection contains materials mainly relating to Throssel's photographic work, including 2,481 photographs, glass plate negatives and lantern slides of the Crow and Northern Cheyenne Indians from 1902-1933.
Biography of Richard Throssel
Throssel (1882-1933) was born in Washington state of Cree Indian and English descent. He worked as an office clerk at the Crow Indian Reservation in south-central Montana from 1902-1910 and was adopted by the Crow tribe in 1905. While at the reservation he met photographer Edward S. Curtis, and was briefly instructed by him. Throssel became a field photographer for the Crow reservation before he established his own photography studio, the Throssel Photocraft Company, in Billings, Montana, in 1910.
Scope and Content
Collection contains materials mainly relating to Throssel's photographic work of the Crow and Northern Cheyenne Indians from 1902-1933. Collection includes 2,481 photographs, glass plate negatives and lantern slides of daily life, ceremonies, portraits and village scenes of the Crow and Northern Cheyenne; what is now the Little Bighorn National Monument; daily life of Billings; Throssel and his family; ranching; and scenery of southern Montana and northern Wyoming (1902-ca. 1920s).
Collection also includes 12 pieces of correspondence with Throssel and of his family (1915-1916, 1928, 1954-1960); manuscripts and speeches by Throssel on Indian culture; newspaper clippings, pamphlets and other printed materials on Throssel and his photography (1900-1963, 1993); 25 paintings by Throssel of outdoor scenes and Crow Indians (1904-1933); and 1 powder horn.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions on the materials for research purposes, and the collection is open to the public.
The photographic positive images may be used by researchers. The use of glass plate negatives requires the permission of the reference archivist.
Related Materials
There are no known other archival collections created by Richard Throssel at the date of processing.
Acquisition Information
The Richard Throssel collection was loaned to the American Heritage Center in 1967 by his daughters, Vera Throssel and Alberta Throssel Hawkins. In 1990 Vera Throssel deeded it to the American Heritage Center.
Existence and Location of Copies
Digital reproductions of select material from this collection are available at http://digitalcollections.uwyo.edu:8180/luna/servlet/uwydbuwy~100~100.
Access Terms
Throssel Family; Throssel Photocraft Company; Cheyenne Indians -- Photographs; Crow Indians -- Photographs; Cheyenne Indians; Crow Indians; Photography -- Montana -- Billings; Photography -- Montana; Photography -- Wyoming; Indians of North America -- Montana; Northern Cheyenne Indian Reservation (Mont.); Crow Indian Reservation (Mont.); Billings (Mont.) -- History; Montana -- History; Little Bighorn Battlefield National Monument (Mont.); Wyoming -- History -- 1890-1918; Wyoming -- History -- 1919-1945; Glass plate negatives; Lantern slides; Negatives; Speeches; Works of art
Arts, Humanities, and Social Sciences; Fine Arts; Social Life and Customs; People, Ethnicity, and Culture; Native Americans; Montana; Wyoming; Photographs
Container List
- Photographs and Negatives, 1902-ca. 1920s; Series I.; 14.86 cubic ft. (6 letter boxes, 1 F24 box, 39 negative boxes, 5 shoe boxes and 4 F20 boxes).
  Most of the 2,481 images in this series are contained in both pictures and negatives. Subjects of the images are mainly Native Americans and outdoor scenes from the early 1900s.
  - 8x10 and 5 x 7 Glass Plate Negatives and Photographs, Subseries I.
    - Man in Ranch Setting (Box 1, Folder 1)
      TP1
      Negative Box 8
      AHC Negative #19256
      Throssel #1
      1 Print
      1 glass negative, 6 ½ x 8 ½
    - "The Muskrat Hunter" (Box 1, Folder 1)
      TP2
      AHC Neg. #25155
      Throssel #4
      2 prints
      2 glass negatives 6½ x 8½
    - "The Muskrat Hunter" (Box 1, Folder 1)
      TP2A
      no print
      1 glass negative 6½ x 8½
      1 glass positive 6½ x 8½
    - "The Rabbit Hunter" (Box 1, Folder 1)
      TP3
      Throssel #5
      1 print
    - "The Rabbit Hunter" (Box 1, Folder 1)
      TP4
      Throssel #6
    - Hunter (Box 1, Folder 1)
      TP5
      Throssel #7
    - Hunter (Box 1, Folder 1)
      TP6
      Throssel #8
    - Procession Through Camp (Box 1, Folder 1)
      TP6A
      Throssel #9
    - Outdoor Cooking (Box 1, Folder 1)
      TP7
      Throssel #10
    - Outdoor Cooking (Box 1, Folder 1)
      TP8
      Throssel #11
    - Walking Through Camp/Winter (Box 1, Folder 2)
      TP9
      AHC Neg. #15656
      Throssel #12
    - Outdoor Cooking/"Barouche" (Box 1, Folder 2)
      TP10
      AHC Neg. #15674
      Throssel #13
      1 glass negative 8 x 10
    - Outdoor Cooking (Box 1, Folder 2)
      TP11
      Throssel #14
    - "Dinner Under the Willows" (Box 1, Folder 2)
      TP12
      Throssel ID #8V008 "©"05
      Throssel #15
      1 glass positive 8 x 10
    - Outdoor Cooking (Box 1, Folder 2)
      TP13
      Throssel #16
    - Man Outside a Tipi (Box 1, Folder 2)
      TP14
      Throssel #20
    - "The Family Fireside" (Box 1, Folder 2)
      TP15
      Throssel ID #6864 "©"07
      Throssel #78
    - "Watching Division of Beef" (Box 1, Folder 2)
      TP16
      Throssel ID #1-6
      Throssel #102
    - Division of Beef (Box 1, Folder 2)
      TP17
      Throssel ID #1-5
      Throssel #104
    - "The Ford" Variation (Box 1, Folder 2)
      TP18
      AHC Neg. #19185
      Throssel #105
    - "The Ford" Variation (Box 1, Folder 2)
      TP19
      Throssel #106
    - Tipis by River (Box 1, Folder 3)
      TP20
      Throssel ID #6878 "©"07
      Throssel #107
    - "The Shell Gatherer" (Box 1, Folder 3)
      TP21
      Negative Box 9
      Throssel ID #6V004 "©"05
      Throssel #108
      4 prints
      1 nitrate negative 6½ x 8½
      1 nitrate positive 6½ x 8½
    - Woman by River (Box 1, Folder 3)
      TP22
      Throssel #109
    - Girls by River (Box 1, Folder 3)
      TP23
      Throssel #110
    - Bathers (Box 1, Folder 3)
      TP24
      Throssel #111
    - "Taking a Swim" (Box 1, Folder 3)
      TP25
      Throssel #112
    - Bathers (Box 1, Folder 3)
      TP26
      Throssel #113
    - Group Bathers (Box 1, Folder 3)
      TP27
      Throssel #114
    - "The Water Carrier" (Box 1, Folder 4)
      TP28
      Throssel #116
      3 prints
    - "The Ford" Variation (Box 1, Folder 4)
      TP29
      Throssel #None
      no negative
    - "The Ford" Variation (Box 1, Folder 4)
      TP29A
    - "The Ford" (Box 1, Folder 4)
      TP30
      Throssel ID #6847 "©"07
      Throssel #117
      2 glass positives 6½ x 8½
    - "The Ford" Variation (Box 1, Folder 4)
      TP31
      Throssel #118
    - "Crossing the River" (Women) (Box 1, Folder 4)
      TP32
      Throssel #119
    - Camp Scene - Winter Horses (Box 1, Folder 5)
      TP33
      Throssel #120
    - "Crossing the Little Big Horn" (Woman) (Box 1, Folder 5)
      TP34
      Throssel ID #6V003 "©"05
      Throssel #121
    - Battle Reenactment (Box 1, Folder 5)
      TP35
      Throssel ID #1-9
      Throssel #72
      1 glass negative 5 x 7
    - "The Fight by the Rimrocks" (Box 1, Folder 5)
      TP36
      Throssel ID #1-12
      Throssel #123
    - Battle Reenactment Showing Photographers (Box 1, Folder 5)
      TP37
      Throssel #124
    - Battle Reenactment (Box 1, Folder 5)
      TP38
      Throssel #125
    - Battle Reenactment (Box 1, Folder 5)
      TP39
    - "The Ford" Variation (Box 1, Folder 5)
      TP40
      Throssel ID #6V034 "©"1911 "©"1909
      2 nitrate negatives 6½ x 8½
      1 glass positive 4 x 5
    - "The Ford" Variation (Box 1, Folder 5)
      TP41
      Negative Box 54
      Throssel ID #6945 "©"08
      Throssel #71
      1 glass positive 6½ x 8½ (broken)
      1 glass positive 5 x 7
    - "The Raiders" (Box 1, Folder 5)
      TP42
      Negative Box 10
      Throssel ID #"©"1907
      3 nitrate negatives 6½ x 8½
    - "The Other Medicine" (Box 1, Folder 6)
      TP43
      Throssel #103
    - "The Other Medicine" (Box 1, Folder 6)
      TP43A
      2 glass negatives 8 x 10
    - Women, Horses, Tipi (Box 1, Folder 6)
      TP44
      Throssel ID #6840 "©"07
      Throssel #151
    - Village Scene (Box 1, Folder 6)
      TP45
      Throssel ID #6X002 "©"09
      Throssel #153
    - Sweat Lodge Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 6)
      TP46
      Throssel #155
    - Sweat Lodge Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 6)
      TP47
      Throssel #156
    - Sweat Lodge Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 6)
      TP48
      Throssel #157
    - Sweat Lodge Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 6)
      TP49
      Throssel #158
    - Sweat Lodge Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 6)
      TP50
      Throssel #159
    - Woman Wood Gatherer (Box 1, Folder 6)
      TP51
      Throssel #160
    - Woman Wood Gatherer (Box 1, Folder 6)
      TP52
      Throssel #161
    - Woman Wood Gatherer (Box 1, Folder 6)
      TP53
      Throssel #162
    - "The Cheyenne Water Girls" (Box 1, Folder 7)
      TP54
      Negative Box 11
      Throssel ID #68030 "©"1911
      Throssel #163
      1 glass negative 4 x 5
    - Night Tipi Scene (Box 1, Folder 7)
      TP55
      AHC Neg. #15655
      Throssel #164
    - Riders Leaving Camp (Box 1, Folder 7)
      TP56
      Throssel ID #6396 "©"07
      Throssel #165
    - Camp Scene - Good Detail of Tipi (Box 1, Folder 7)
      TP57
      Throssel #166
    - Camp Scene (Box 1, Folder 7)
      TP58
      Throssel #167
    - "Indian Caller" (Box 1, Folder 7)
      TP59
      AHC Neg. #15661
      Throssel ID #6X021
      Throssel #168
    - "Indian Caller" (Box 1, Folder 7)
      TP60
      Throssel ID #6X022
      Throssel #169
    - Night Tipi Scene (Box 1, Folder 8)
      TP61
      Throssel #170
    - "The Trapper's Home" (Box 1, Folder 8)
      TP62
      AHC Neg. #15660
      Throssel #171
    - "Camp Fire No. 2" (Box 1, Folder 8)
      TP63
      AHC Neg. #25626
      AHC Neg. #15668
      Throssel ID #6810 "©"07
      Throssel #172
    - River Camp Scene (Box 1, Folder 8)
      TP64
      Throssel ID #6826 "©"08
      Throssel #173
    - River Camp Scene (Box 1, Folder 8)
      TP65
      Throssel ID #6824 "©"08
      Throssel #175
    - Night Tipi Scene (Box 1, Folder 8)
      TP66
      Throssel #176
      1 glass negative 5½ x 7½
    - Crow Couple by Medicine Tipi (Box 1, Folder 8)
      TP67
      Throssel ID #6956
      Throssel #177
    - Children by Tipi (Box 1, Folder 9)
      TP68
      Throssel #178
    - "Song to the Winter Sun" (Box 1, Folder 9)
      TP69
      AHC Neg. #18596
      Throssel ID #6X024 "©"
      Throssel #179
    - Camp Scene (Box 1, Folder 9)
      TP70
      Throssel #180
    - Camp Scene (Box 1, Folder 9)
      TP71
      Throssel #181
    - Camp Scene (Box 1, Folder 9)
      TP72
      Throssel #182
    - Camp Scene - Winter (Box 1, Folder 9)
      TP73
      Throssel ID #6873 "©"07
      Throssel #183
    - Two Men by Tipi/Campfire (Box 1, Folder 9)
      TP74
      Throssel #184
    - Camp Scene (Box 1, Folder 9)
      TP75
      Throssel ID #8V004 "©"07
      Throssel #185
    - "After the War" (Box 1, Folder 10)
      TP76
      Negative Box 12
      Throssel ID #6051 "©"08
      Throssel #186
    - "After the War" (Box 1, Folder 10)
      TP76A
      1 nitrate negative 3½ x 4½
    - Women Making Pemmican (Box 1, Folder 10)
      TP77
      Throssel #187
    - Women Preparing a Hide (Box 1, Folder 10)
      TP78
      Throssel #188
      2 glass negatives 5 x 7
    - Women Preparing a Hide (Box 1, Folder 10)
      TP78A
    - Meat Drying/Tipi/Hewn Logs (Box 1, Folder 10)
      TP79
      Throssel ID #6936 "©"08
      Throssel #189
    - Meat Drying/Tipi (Box 1, Folder 10)
      TP79A
    - Women Preparing a Hide (Box 1, Folder 10)
      TP80
      Throssel #190
    - Women Preparing a Hide (Box 1, Folder 10)
      TP81
      Throssel #191
    - Women Preparing a Hide (Box 1, Folder 10)
      TP82
    - "The Mourner" (Box 1, Folder 10)
      TP83
      Throssel ID #6925 "©"08
      Throssel #193
    - "The Travois" (Box 1, Folder 11)
      TP84
      Throssel ID #6X025
      Throssel #194
    - "The Travois" (Box 1, Folder 11)
      TP84A
    - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 11)
      TP85
      Throssel #2
    - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 11)
      TP86
      Throssel #18
    - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 11)
      TP87
      Throssel #19
    - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 11)
      TP88
      Negative Box 13
      Throssel #21
    - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 11)
      TP89
      Throssel #115
    - Moving into Sun Lodge (Box 1, Folder 11)
      TP90
      Throssel ID #6975 "©"09
      Throssel #174
    - "Raising the Clan Poles in the Sun Dance Lodge" (Box 1, Folder 12)
      TP91
      Throssel #246
    - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 12)
      TP92
      Throssel #247
    - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 12)
      TP93
      Throssel #248
    - "The Dance" (Box 1, Folder 12)
      TP94
      Throssel ID #6977 "©"09
      Throssel #249
    - "The Redman's Lodge" (Box 1, Folder 12)
      TP95
      Throssel ID #6978 "©"09
      Throssel #250
    - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 12)
      TP96
      Throssel ID #6980 "©"09
      Throssel #251
    - "Blessing the Feast" (Box 1, Folder 13)
      TP97
      Throssel ID #6979 "©"09
      Throssel #252
    - "Blessing the Feast" (Box 1, Folder 13)
      TP98
      Throssel ID #6983 "©"09
      Throssel #253
    - Ceremony with Four Men - Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 13)
      TP99
      Throssel #258
    - "Last Salute to the Sun Gods" - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 13)
      TP100
      AHC Neg. #26025
      Throssel ID #6982 "©"09
      Throssel #259
    - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 13)
      TP101
      Throssel #260
    - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 13)
      TP101A
      Throssel #276
    - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 13)
      TP102
      Throssel #261
    - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 13)
      TP103
      Throssel #262
    - "Salute to Sun Gods" (Box 1, Folder 13)
      TP104
      Throssel #263
    - "Salute To Sun Gods" (Box 1, Folder 13)
      TP105
      Throssel #264
    - "Raising the Sun Pole" (Box 1, Folder 13)
      TP106
      Throssel ID #6973 "©"09
      Throssel #265
    - "Raising the Sun Pole" (Box 1, Folder 14)
      TP107
      Throssel #266
    - "The Dance" (Box 1, Folder 14)
      TP108
      Throssel ID #6981 "©"09
      Throssel #267
    - "Preparing the Sun Pole" (Box 1, Folder 14)
      TP109
      Throssel ID #6972 "©"09
      Throssel #268
    - "Preparing the Sun Pole" (Box 1, Folder 14)
      TP110
      Throssel #269
    - "Preparing the Sun Pole" (Box 1, Folder 14)
      TP111
      Throssel #270
    - "Last of the Sun Dance" (Box 1, Folder 14)
      TP112
      Throssel #290
    - Sun Dance [?] (Box 1, Folder 14)
      TP113
      Throssel #322
    - Sun Dance [?] (Box 1, Folder 14)
      TP114
      Throssel #323
    - "Painting the Dancers" (Box 1, Folder 14)
      TP115
      Negative Box 14
      Throssel ID #6976 "©"09
      Throssel #324
    - "The Dance Ended" (Box 1, Folder 15)
      TP116
      Throssel ID #6986 "©"09
      Throssel #325
    - "The Leader" - Sun Dance (Box 1, Folder 15)
      TP117
      AHC Neg. #26026
      Throssel ID #6971 "©"09
      Throssel #703
    - Cheyenne Animal Dance (Box 1, Folder 15)
      TP118
      Throssel #32
    - Cheyenne Animal Dance (Box 1, Folder 15)
      TP119
      Throssel #38
      1 celluloid negative 4 x 5
    - Cheyenne Animal Dance (Box 1, Folder 15)
      TP120
      Throssel #46
    - Cheyenne Animal Dance (Box 1, Folder 15)
      TP121
      Throssel #58
    - Cheyenne Animal Dance (Box 1, Folder 15)
      TP122
      Throssel #67
    - Cheyenne Animal Dance (Box 1, Folder 15)
      TP123
      Throssel #73
    - "The Animal Dance" (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP124
      Throssel #237
      1 nitrate negative 5 x 7
    - "The Departing Spirit" (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP125
      Throssel #301
    - Cheyenne Animal Dance (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP126
      Throssel #940
    - Cheyenne Animal Dance (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP127
      Throssel #960
    - "The Animal Dance" (See Edward Curtis Vol. VI) (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP128
      Throssel #977
    - Cheyenne Animal Dance (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP129
    - Cheyenne Animal Dance (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP130
    - Animal Dance [?] (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP130A
    - "The Adoption Ceremony" - Cheyenne Animal Dance (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP131
      Throssel #236
    - Cheyenne Contraries (village scene) (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP132
      Throssel #24
    - Cheyenne Contraries (group of Indians constructing tipis) (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP133
      Throssel #29
    - Cheyenne Contraries (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP134
      Throssel #30
    - Cheyenne Contraries (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP135
      Throssel #35
    - Cheyenne Contraries (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP136
      Negative Box 15
      Throssel #44
    - Cheyenne Contraries (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP137
      Throssel #76
    - Cheyenne Contraries (Box 1, Folder 16)
      TP138
      Throssel #77
    - Crow Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 17)
      TP139
      Throssel #3
    - "Mixing Medicine Tobacco Seed for Planting" (Box 1, Folder 17)
      TP140
      Throssel #17
      1 glass negative 6½ x 8½ (broken)
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony Altar (Box 1, Folder 17)
      TP141
      Throssel #25
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 17)
      TP142
      Throssel #54
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 17)
      TP143
      Throssel #96
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 17)
      TP144
      Throssel #98
    - Watching Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 17)
      TP145
      Throssel ID #1-4
      Throssel #122
    - The Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 18)
      TP146
      Throssel ID #6934 "©"08
      Throssel #152
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony - The Planting (Box 1, Folder 18)
      TP147
      Throssel #233
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 17)
      TP148
      Throssel #234
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony - The Planting (Box 1, Folder 18)
      TP149
      Throssel #235
    - The Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 18)
      TP150
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 18)
      TP151
      Throssel #277
    - "Crow Tobacco Dance - Initiating a Younger Novice into a Clan" (Box 1, Folder 18)
      TP152
      AHC Neg. #25157
      Throssel ID #"©"
      Throssel #277A
      5 prints
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 19)
      TP153
      Throssel #279
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 19)
      TP154
      Throssel #280
    - "The Adoption Ceremony" (Box 1, Folder 19)
      TP155
      Throssel #281
    - "The Adoption Ceremony" (Box 1, Folder 19)
      TP156
      Throssel #282
    - "The Adoption Ceremony" (Box 1, Folder 19)
      TP157
      Throssel #283
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 19)
      TP158
      Throssel #284
    - Feast after Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 19)
      TP159
      Throssel #285
    - "A Tobacco Dance" (Box 1, Folder 19)
      TP160
      Throssel ID #8V010
      Throssel #288
    - "A Tobacco Dance" (Box 1, Folder 19)
      TP161
      Throssel #289
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 19)
      TP162
      Throssel ID #6933 "©"08
      Throssel #303
    - "Singing his Medicine Song" (Box 1, Folder 20)
      TP163
      Negative Box 16
      Throssel #304
    - "An Initiation Ceremony - Medicine Tobacco Dance" (Box 1, Folder 20)
      TP164
      Throssel ID # 6899 "©"07
      Throssel #320
    - "An Initiation Ceremony - Medicine Tobacco Dance" (Box 1, Folder 20)
      TP164A
      Throssel ID #6899 "©"07
      Throssel #321
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 20)
      TP165
      Throssel #326
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 20)
      TP166
      Throssel #327
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 20)
      TP167 and TP167A
      Throssel #328 and #328A
    - Feast at the Tobacco Dance (Box 1, Folder 20)
      TP168
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 20)
      TP169
      Throssel #962
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 20)
      TP170
      Throssel #968
    - Medicine Tobacco Ceremony (Box 1, Folder 20)
      TP171
      Throssel #788
    - "The Arrow Game" (Crow) (Box 1, Folder 21)
      TP172
      Throssel #254
    - The Arrow Game (Box 1, Folder 21)
      TP173
      Throssel #255
    - The Arrow Game (Box 1, Folder 21)
      TP174
      Throssel ID #6X002
      Throssel #256
    - "The Game of Arrows" (Box 1, Folder 21)
      TP175
      AHC Neg. #25707
      Throssel #257
    - Dance - Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 21)
      TP176
      AHC Neg. #19188
      Throssel #278
    - Event Unidentified (Possible Giveaway) (Box 1, Folder 21)
      TP177
      Throssel ID #6952 "©"08 (?)
      Throssel #74
    - Event Unidentified (Possible Giveaway) (Box 1, Folder 21)
      TP177A
      Throssel #286
      1 glass positive 7 x 6½
    - "War Dance" (Box 1, Folder 22)
      TP178
      Throssel #287
      1 glass negative 8 x 10 (broken)
    - "War Dance" (Box 1, Folder 22)
      TP179
    - War Dance (Box 1, Folder 22)
      TP180
      AHC Neg. #19189
      Throssel ID #8V011
      Throssel #291
    - War Dance (Box 1, Folder 22)
      TP181
      Throssel ID #8V015
      Throssel #292
    - Gift Dance (Box 1, Folder 22)
      TP182
      Throssel ID #8V012
      Throssel #293
    - "Caravan Dance" (Box 1, Folder 22)
      TP183
      Negative Box 17
      Throssel ID #6859 "©"07
      Throssel #294
    - "Caravan Dance" (Box 1, Folder 22)
      TP183A
      AHC Neg. #19187
      Throssel #295
    - Night Dances (Box 1, Folder 22)
      TP184
      Throssel #296
      1 glass negative 6½ x 7
    - "A Song in the Scalp Dance" (Also Labeled "Owl Dance") (Box 1, Folder 22)
      TP185
      AHC Neg. #19190
      Throssel #297
      2 glass positives 8 x 10
    - "Sioux War Dance" (Box 1, Folder 23)
      TP186
      AHC Neg. #19193
      Throssel #298
    - "Sioux War Dance" (Box 1, Folder 23)
      TP187
      Throssel #299
    - "Sioux War Dance" (Box 1, Folder 23)
      TP188
      Throssel #300
    - "Sioux War Dance" (Box 1, Folder 23)
      TP189
      Throssel #302
    - Singers (Box 1, Folder 23)
      TP190
      Throssel ID #6757
      Throssel #305
    - Singers (Box 1, Folder 23)
      TP190A
    - Male Dancers - Posed (Box 1, Folder 23)
      TP191
      Throssel #306
    - Two Men on Horses - Ceremonial Dress (Box 1, Folder 23)
      TP192
      Throssel #307
    - Two Children On Horse (Box 1, Folder 23)
      TP193 and TP193A
      Throssel #308
    - Men on Horseback - Ceremonial Dress (Box 1, Folder 24)
      TP194
      Throssel #309
    - Men on Horseback - Ceremonial Dress (Box 1, Folder 24)
      TP194A
    - Warrior on Horseback - Full Headdress (Box 1, Folder 24)
      TP195 and TP195A
      Throssel ID #6868 "©"07
      Throssel #310
    - Rider Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 24)
      TP196
      Throssel #311
    - Rider Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 24)
      TP197
      Throssel #312
    - Rider Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 24)
      TP198
      Throssel ID #6836 "©"07
      Throssel #313
    - Rider Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 24)
      TP199
      Negative Box 18
      Throssel ID #6901 "©"07
      Throssel #314
    - Three Crow Men on Horseback (Box 1, Folder 24)
      TP200
      Throssel #315
    - "The Medicine Man's Daughter" (Box 1, Folder 24)
      TP201
      Throssel #316
      1 glass positive 6 x 7
    - "Two Old Timers" (Box 1, Folder 24)